(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Hello.
(Penny:)What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard's mad at me,
so I'm making him lemon bars.
(Penny:)Does he even
like lemon bars?
(Sheldon:)Not really.
(Sheldon:)But I'm mad at him, too,
so lemon bars it is.
(Penny:)Something happen
at the meeting?
(Sheldon:)They made me promise
I wouldn't talk.
(Penny:)And you talked?
(Sheldon:)Well, now, see?
(Sheldon:)You knew what was gonna
happen. Why didn't they?
(Sheldon:)Anyway, now we're committed
to completing this project
(Sheldon:)in a ridiculously
short time frame,
(Sheldon:)and everyone's
upset with me.
(Penny:)Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
(Penny:)Bernadette's mad at me, too.
Mm. If it makes you
feel any better,
(Sheldon:)a parasitoid wasp known
as Oobius depressus
(Sheldon:)has been rediscovered
after 101 years
(Sheldon:)of presumed extinction.
(Penny:)Why would that
make me feel better?
(Sheldon:)Why would your Bernadette
thing make me feel better?
(Sheldon:)At least mine
was educational.
(Penny:)Okay. Never mind.